expertmobi.com 2019-04-26

# Privacy Policy

The following describes the overall company privacy policy (the “Privacy Policy”) of ExpertMobi (hereinafter referred to as the “Company”). The Privacy Policy was created to inform you what information we collect when you visit this website (hereinafter referred to as “website”,“us”, “we” or “our”) as well as our customer's ("Advertisers") websites; as well as how that information is collected and used by companies that display advertisements ("Partners" or “Publishers”). 

The Company reserves the right to update the policy periodically, and these updates are effective upon posting. It is imperative that this document is read thoroughly and often. 

### Collection of Information

The Company does not seek any personal information by illegal means. We collect only necessary information from you and other individuals who use the website (Advertisers and Partners) by means of online or offline surveys, order forms, registration pages, telephone or cell phone communication, and other similar means. 

Personally Related Information (“PRI”) is an information the Company may ask you and other individuals who use the website (Advertisers and Partners) to provide. It may include your name, email address, street address, zip code/postal code, telephone numbers (including wireless phone numbers, birth date, gender, salary range, education and marital status, occupation, social security number, employment information, personal and online interests, and any other additional information that may be requested from time to time. 

Non-Personally Related Information ("NPRI") is information collected by the Company concerning the computer system that the individual is using to access Company's website — such as IP address, date and time of visit, domain type, and their activity, browser type, browser language, referring pages, exit pages and visited URLs, platform type, click counts, pages viewed and in what order, time spent, and other important data is necessary to validate and authorize your entry and activity on the website. 

### Cookies

The Company uses Cookies to associate certain Internet-related information about you and other individuals who use the website (Advertisers and Partners) with information about you in our database. A cookie is a small amount of data stored on the hard drive of your computer that allows us to identify you with your corresponding data that resides in our database. 

### Use of Information

The Company will only use information provided by you and other individuals who use the website (Advertisers and Partners) for the reason that you have provided this information for. 

Your PRI will be used to establish your account, to communicate with you and for ongoing record keeping, required by the Company. 

Your NPR Information including cookies etc, will be used only for system administration and for improvement of our services . This ensures our Partners get credited for services they provide to Advertisers, and Advertisers get complete package of services the Company provides. 

### Dissemination of Information

Your Personal Information will not be shared unless we have first given you notice that we might share your data, and you have authorized us to do so. The Company receives information from you and other individuals who use the website (Advertisers and Partners), and have the right to use this data (sometimes, in connection with NPR information), but is generally prohibited from sharing this information with other companies or people. 

Your NPR Information will not be linked with your Personal Information or be shared, unless we have given you notice as described above and you have given us authorization to do so. 

### General Data Protection Regulation

On May 25, 2018, the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) becomes officially operative. The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) (EU) 2016/679 is a regulation in EU law on data protection and privacy for all individuals within the European Union and the European Economic Area. It also addresses the export of personal data outside the EU and EEA. The GDPR aims primarily to give control to citizens and residents over their personal data and to simplify the regulatory environment for international business by unifying the regulation within the EU. 

In accordance with the applicable laws, users are authorized to access and modify their own data held by the companies, which includes data collection, ad tracking, surveys, cookies, location data, and every other bit of a user’s “digital footprint”. Users are also entitled to transmit their personal details to other organizations. The GDPR also enforces companies to determine their in-house data security policies. 

We will, to the best of our ability, make sure that our sub-processors operate in full accordance with GDPR requirements before starting cooperation with them and require such sub-processors to comply with this Privacy Policy and maintain appropriate security to protect user information from unauthorized access or processing, unless we have no ability to do so (for example, where we are sharing information with regulatory authorities or courts). Nevertheless, we cannot be held responsible or liable for the use of any information that a sub-processor may execute, or that is gathered by sub-processors. Whenever applicable, users should acquaint themselves with Privacy Policies of any of the involved sub-processors’ websites. 

We keep personal data for as long as it is necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the personal data was collected or for as long as required by applicable law. 

You (data subject) may send official requests to us regarding your personal data via email to the following address: [dpo@expertmobi.com](mailto:%20dpo@expertmobi.com)

At any time, you have the right: 

  * To access your personal information that we hold;  

  * To request a copy of your personal data;  

  * To request that ExpertMobi corrects your personal data if inaccurate or out of date. If you have a registered account on our websites or online platforms, you can update your personal data directly on your preferences section;  

  * To request the erasure of your personal data when no longer necessary for the purposes for which they are processed;  

  * To withdraw your consent given to us for a certain purpose, for example for targeted advertising;  

  * To request a restriction on further processing, in case there is a dispute regarding the processing;  

  * To object to processing of your personal information by us;  

  * To file a complaint to a supervisory authority in your jurisdiction

Your request will be executed no later than 30 (thirty) days from the initial request receipt but we will do everything possible to process it within the first 48 working hours. 

### Copyright

All Site content, design, text, graphics, images, logos, buttons, icons, interfaces, audio and video clips, and the selection and arrangements thereof are the exclusive property of ExpertMobi, or its respective content providers, and are protected by international copyright laws. All software used on the Site is the property of ExpertMobi or its respective software suppliers, and such software is protected by international copyright laws and other applicable laws and treaties. Users of this Site shall not transmit/post any information to this Site that infringes the copyright or other intellectual property rights of others. 

In case you have any other queries regarding privacy information, please contact us at [support@expertmobi.com](mailto:%20support@expertmobi.com)
